Motor Cover Throttle: Even if this part is installed in your vehicle,
ICICI also provides its recycling under
service.  You can see that
my car has all the scratches of Dear which
I had mentioned in my claim and sent to the centre.
So hello friends welcome
back to my new video.  For the last few days,
you must have seen that my Ola S1X
kw variant, which I purchased
in October 2024, used to have the
problem of RS Nagin.  You guys must have
noticed that the MCU of my car has also been
changed.  I had posted the video here
that the MCU of my car was changed.
For which those Ola people had taken 10 to
15 days for the car and now
they told me that the
BAMS of my car is bad, which
they had told me at the LIG Ola service center.
So my car stayed there also for 5 to 7
days.  So he did not order BAMS.
Meaning it took a lot of time.  So after
cleaning my car, I mean my
insurance company
towed my car and
sent it to the service centre of LA in Palda which is
in Indore itself. Basically, there are only
two service centres of Ola in Indore, one
is at Palda and the other is at LI. The
video which you people are watching right now is of the
service centre of LIG which is
in Ola Indore.  In this also many
vehicles are parked here.  So
they checked my car.  He said that there is a
BAMS problem in my car.   If
BAMS is going to be installed in my car then I will have to place an
order for it.  That will take a lot of time.
So I left my car there.
These people
installed their software which is like a box in my car and found out
what problem there was in the car and
what problem there was not.  So
they said that they will install BMS of the vehicle.
But a lot of time had passed, so I got my
car towed and took the insurance plan
provided to me by the insurance company, which is my ICICI LB
plan.  So
they towed my
car and sent it there.  Ok?
So, first of all I saw
what had happened in my car.  And the
problem I had with my car was that the coupler wire of my car was
cut.  Rats etc. had
cut the wires of my car.  Due to which my car's
battery was not showing its percentage and range
and it was showing cold service and system
issue on the screen.  So,
I towed it and sent it to my service centre at
Palda.  So then he repaired my car there.  That
means the
wires etc. that they had connected.  So then
you all must have noticed that there were
many scratches etc. on my car due to which the
car looked quite useless.  A lot of
scratches etc., the banner panels of the car were broken.  So because of that
my car looked very bad.
So we had also taken his insurance
to claim it.  Because my
car was insured by IC LB company.
So I had taken approval from him to
claim insurance for my car
and there I had
told everything about my car.  So
you guys can see in this photo how
many scratches are there on my car, the
car is completely broken from all sides,
which means every panel is broken.  You
can see that the person who placed his feet on the sides etc. of the
car also got broken.  You can see this
above the light, it means it is broken.
So because of that I have claimed insurance for my car.  The one who owns
Ola's service center.  So
we took our car there and
they told us to leave the car there.
So I left my car there.
Due to which he said that
you have insurance, put it for claim.
Once the approval comes, we will
order the parts for your vehicle and tell you
what parts will be installed in your vehicle.
So I also left my car there.  There was
no problem in that.
Then after a few days, a message comes about my own car.  You
can see that dear customer your claim has been
registered.  MOT means
your claim has been registered.  Meaning he
registered his claim.  Then
their surveyor said that they will fit these parts in your vehicle,
which you can see, Total
Gear ICIC will not fit all these parts in their vehicles
and they also told on WhatsApp that
brother, the surveyor inspector has
checked your vehicle, Damn,
whatever is in your vehicle has been checked by Aman, ICIC LBD
company will tell you that they will fit the
parts in their vehicle.  So you people must have seen
this part in my car, they had
told that they will not put this part in my car,
their inspector had
asked to put this part at Ola's service
center, which they had told to the agent, so
you people can see that this ICIC LBD company
person had sent a message on WhatsApp, they message on the same number in whose
name the vehicle is, the registered number
in their insurance policy, in this, it
means everyone
tells that this is what is there in your car, that is
ICIC Lob Tax, a simple text message also
came in which they told everything that your ID has been
inspected and your
vehicle has been put for approval or when the
approval comes from the company, then they will
start the work on your vehicle and will update you about
what parts they will put in the vehicle.  You
can see that this is how we send messages, we give
ourselves all the updates through messages
and the experience of Ola's insurance
people here is also quite good.  The
insurance people talk nicely.  It is
not like that, it is like service.  The
service people talk in a very bad manner.  The
rest of the insurance companies
work well.  Without informing them,
they get all the vehicle claims etc. done for them.
So those people made
me download this app which you
can see.  IC
IC Eye Care, in which everyone tells that their car means
their own, that they had
registered the claim in this app, in which
they had written everything about what happened to the car,
so I had written in my claim
that a dog came in front of me, so I suddenly
applied the brakes of the car and the car fell.
I had written this in my claim and had
taken the driving license of the person who was
driving the car.  I had asked for the train time.  At
what time did the car fall?  Where did it
fall, they asked for all these
basic details like what all fell in your car,
where, when, how it fell and who was the driver,
how much driving experience did the driver have, they
ask for all these details, so
if you ever make a claim then give it in a valid form, so keep it
in your mind that if
I ever ask for exactly this, then these people are
not like that to ask because whatever work has been done for me has been done
without any call.
He didn't even call me.
He did all my work here without even calling me.
I did not face any problem in this.  You
can see that through this app you can insure your
other vehicles also.  For example, if
I have to
claim for my bike, then I can claim for the bike also.  If you want to
claim any other vehicle, you
can claim it.  There is
no problem of his own in that.  All your details are
coming here.  Claim status of the vehicle,
how much is the expense on the vehicle.  The current cost of my car is ₹7000.
Which is more than ₹7000.  Let
me tell you further that
all the details of your vehicle are also available in your Ola app.
What new things will be added to the car?  All parts are
getting infected.  Part charges, labour charges
etc. can be seen by all.  Vinay Tiwari
is the insurance of ICIC Low LMD.  Ola SFX
is a 3k variant.  And in our Ola
app, all the details are being given
in the Ola app which is our vehicle under
service.  And in this you can see that it is
telling the location of your vehicle etc.
How far is it from my house?  The Palda one
is parked at Ola's service centre which is located
in Indore.  And in this everyone is
also telling about their parts etc. which I will show you.  Let's
see the ticket number ongoing tickets.   If
you click on this, then
all the parts etc. of your vehicle are being told here.  If you go into it, you
can see here, it is telling everything, you
can see motor cover, throttle grip etc., all
your labor waivers, you can see everything here, you
can stop it and read what kind of
parts they are, how much they cost, you can also
claim insurance for your vehicle, so you should
try to get all your small parts
replaced
because if you face any problem in future, they have
already been replaced, you will not have to pay from your pocket, so you
can see that
more than half of the parts of my vehicle have also been
replaced here, so if you also want to make a claim, then
you can do this process,
tell the valid reason for claiming insurance.
So friends, if you liked the video then please
like the video and if you are visiting this channel for the
first time then please subscribe to the channel.
Thank you so much for watching.  See you
soon in the next video and if you have any
queries etc. related to Ola then you
can comment.  I
reply to every comment of yours.  Thank you so much
for watching.  See you soon
in the next video.